{"text": "Lisa,\n\nI apologize for the delay!  This is a new one for us and they are taking their sweet time on getting the paper work back to us.  I have copied Pam LaRue on this email as you can see and she will respond to you on how that process is going.\n\nRhonda", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [150, 159, "PERSON"], [248, 254, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Leo/Monika,\n\nMea culpa.  I forgot to include you on my distribution list.  Sorry.\n\nKC", "labels": [[0, 10, "ORG"], [13, 16, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "We are assuming we will be physical on Monday Feb 11 in Canada.\nLet me know if there is an issue.", "labels": [[56, 62, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Rick, \n\nWhat is Rudi Zipter's status?  He has sent a couple of emails to Bobbi Tessandori our immigration representative .  He has taken vacation and paternity and repatriated back to the US.  Is he working in the office? Is he going to be retained? Please advise.\n\nRegards,\nFrank  ", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [16, 29, "PERSON"], [73, 89, "PERSON"], [188, 190, "GPE"], [275, 280, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Lisa,\n\n     Breakfast sandwiches and coffee could be in order this morn.   Let me know if you are down and when you can go.    Also tell Jsarnow.\n\nlate,\nDarren", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [137, 144, "ORG"], [153, 159, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "This is a presentation I put together for Derek, but it was some general info that may be of interest to you.\n\nLet me know if and when you guys would like to sit down and go over Ontario in a bit me detail at some point over the next week. You can also get a good fundies overview from the IMO forecasts at:\n\nhttp://www.iemo.com/imoweb/monthsYears/monthsAhead.asp", "labels": [[309, 336, "url"], [42, 47, "PERSON"], [179, 186, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "We were cut 40 MW today by BPA for peak hours on 6/18 at COB on enpower deal number 305699. Lisa purchased replacement power from Avista at $30. Enpower 897712\n\nWe presold power to Avista at $33.50 for the month and are now buying it back from them at $30 to book out.  Of course, BPA should not charge us for the 27.25 supply price under their contract.\n\n\nMo Elafandi \nEnron North America \n121 SW Salmon, 3WTC0407\nPortland, OR 97204 \n503-464-5106 \nFax 503-464-7376\nCellular 503-860-8564", "labels": [[83, 90, "phone"], [27, 30, "ORG"], [57, 60, "ORG"], [92, 96, "PERSON"], [130, 136, "ORG"], [181, 187, "ORG"], [281, 284, "ORG"], [370, 389, "ORG"], [415, 423, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Greg,\n\n\nFurther to my email to you earlier today, we have tracked down the reasons for the discrepancies in the termination dates in your list versus the chart we have prepared.  In many instances, that contract was reviewed by BCG, and it was determined that the wrong termination date was set, given the provisions of the contract.  I understand that a memo with respect to this issue likely was forwarded to ECC by Chris Christopher and John Eamon on January 8, 2002 ( a copy of which is attached), which set out that based on our review of the contracts, the following parties and their proper termination dates are:\n\nAEC Marketing, physical, gas  - February 1, 2002\nCalpine Canada Natural Gas Partnership (Encal) physical, gas - February 1, 2002\nEl Paso Merchant Energy, physical gas - February 1, 2002\nWilliams Energy Marketing & Trade Co. - February 1, 2002\n\nOur review last night also revealed the following:\nBaytex physical, gas- ECC list says terminated January 6/02, but the January 4/02 letter from ECC set a termination date of January 8/02, which is reflected in the Chart\n\nMarathon Canada Limited physical, gas - ECC list says terminated December 18/01, however the chart suggests that this was revised by a letter from ECC, sent December 31, 01, changing the termination date to January 4/02.  Chris Christopher recalls the letter, but we do not have a copy of that letter.\n\nCalpine Canada Natural Gas Partnership (Orbit) physical, gas - we have reviewed the contract and determined that the chart is incorrect.  It has been changed from February 1/02 to December 18/01, as set out in the ECC list.\n\nI understand that you have reviewed the Cinergy contract and determined the reason for the discrepancy in that instance.\n\nWe continue our review of a couple of entries, namely Canadian Natural Resources, Talisman Energy Inc, and Dynegy Canada.  The remainder of the list was either consistent with the Chart, or had no entry and was therefore updated with your information.\n\nThank you for forwarding this to our attention.\n\n\n\n\n\n\nBryan C. Duguid\nPartner\nBlake, Cassels & Graydon LLP\n3500, 855 Second Street SW\nCalgary, AB  T2P 4J8\n\nTel: 403.260.9716\nFax: 403.260.9700\nE-mail:  bryan.duguid@blakes.com\n\nThis e-mail communication is confidential and legally privileged. If you are not the intended recipient, please notify me at the telephone number shown above or by return e-mail and delete this communication and any copy immediately. Thank you.", "labels": [[2192, 2215, "email"], [2192, 2204, "url"], [464, 470, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [228, 231, "ORG"], [411, 414, "ORG"], [418, 435, "PERSON"], [440, 450, "PERSON"], [671, 709, "ORG"], [751, 774, "ORG"], [808, 845, "ORG"], [917, 923, "ORG"], [1011, 1014, "ORG"], [1235, 1238, "ORG"], [1310, 1327, "PERSON"], [1391, 1429, "ORG"], [1656, 1663, "ORG"], [1792, 1818, "ORG"], [1820, 1839, "ORG"], [1845, 1858, "ORG"], [2045, 2060, "PERSON"], [2069, 2093, "ORG"], [2125, 2132, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "The following expense report is ready for approval:\n\nEmployee Name: Richard L. Carson\nStatus last changed by: Rita J. Hennessy\nExpense Report Name: January  2002\nReport Total: $136.17\nAmount Due Employee: $136.17\n\n\nTo approve this expense report, click on the following link for Concur Expense.\nhttp://expensexms.enron.com", "labels": [[295, 318, "url"], [156, 161, "phone"], [68, 92, "PERSON"], [110, 127, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Lisa I will need to call Hafslund today and request their December 01 detail.\n\nThanks\n\nMark\n\n713-345-7179", "labels": [[93, 100, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Please find attached Competitive Intelligence's current assessment of recen=\nt events in several emerging markets, particularly Argentina.  As the situa=\ntion there appears to be getting more dire, we will continue monitoring the=\n potential ramifications for other emerging markets such as Brazil.  Please=\n note that this information is highly proprietary and should not be shared =\noutside Enron Industrial Markets.  Additionally, if you have any further qu=\nestions, please feel free to forward them to me as Brendan Fitzsimmons supp=\norts a very broad audience and may not be able to field the request.  Thank=\ns.", "labels": [[128, 137, "GPE"], [226, 230, "ORG"], [291, 297, "GPE"], [393, 417, "ORG"], [513, 532, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Lisa,\n\nMark is the one that is taking care of that CP and he is not in today.Sabrina Minnis is original coordinator and I asked if she had copies of the information for Hafslund and she replied that she gave it information to Mark Confer.  I'll leave him a note letting him know what you need. The Hafslund issue that I was working with is dealing with the month of Jan 2001. Let me know if I could be of any more assistance to you.\n\nKa'Tina-", "labels": [[71, 84, "url"], [369, 374, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [7, 11, "PERSON"], [51, 53, "ORG"], [77, 91, "PERSON"], [169, 177, "GPE"], [226, 237, "PERSON"], [298, 306, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Both for all of Dec and or any day that has discrepancy.\nThanks!\n\nlisa", "labels": []}
{"text": "Lisa,\n\n\tDO you need the detail the Enron has for Hafslund or the detail from Hasfslund or Dec 01?\n\nKa'Tina", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [35, 40, "ORG"], [49, 57, "GPE"], [77, 86, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "My apologies if this has been done, but I'm in process of assembling list of products that UBS will be trading.  If this list has been compiled, please direct it to me.  \n\nI'm interested in getting the greatest granularity possible breaking it out by VaR portfolio name, trader, trading book, commodity, instrument, location, tenor, relative liquidity for each instrument expressed in contract/day (i.e. could impact holding period for VAR) and best risk mitigator.  (Regarding best risk mitigator, I'm not looking for liquidating position comments, but rather best hedge given curve location.)  This will help in directing correlation efforts for VAR.  See attached spreadsheet for suggested format.\n\nThanks,\nFrank", "labels": [[399, 402, "url"], [91, 94, "ORG"], [710, 715, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Holly:  The instructions for access to ECN 2886 provided by Sharon Sullo should remain in effect and Sharon and myself are now the authorized approvers of access authority.  These changes were authorized by Rick Buy, Chief Risk Officer.  Please call me if you have questions.  Regards!    Rick Carson", "labels": [[42, 48, "phone"], [0, 5, "PERSON"], [60, 72, "PERSON"], [101, 107, "PERSON"], [207, 215, "PERSON"], [289, 300, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "John,\n\nAttached is a spreadsheet that outlines the transactions with the Power Pool\ntoday, specifically the $6.95 M that will be withheld as a security deposit\nfor Enron Canada Power Corp.  If you have any questions or concerns, please\ngive me a call.\n\n <<Enron Security Jan 29 2002.xls>>\n\nCarol Moline\nFinancial Controller\nPower Pool of Alberta\n(403) 233-4686\ncarol.moline@powerpool.ab.ca", "labels": [[361, 389, "email"], [278, 286, "url"], [274, 281, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [164, 188, "ORG"], [256, 277, "ORG"], [290, 303, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Next weeks Management Committee meeting will take place on Tuesday January 29 at 11:00am in the boardroom instead of Monday.\n\nRegards,\nSue\n________________________________\n\nSue Ford\nEnron Corp.\nTel: 713-853-5176\nFax: 713-646-5930\nsue.ford@enron.com", "labels": [[230, 248, "email"], [230, 238, "url"], [74, 83, "phone"], [11, 31, "ORG"], [177, 181, "ORG"], [182, 193, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Lisa:\n\nThanks for the info. yesterday. We are almost there with BPA in December.  Attached is the remaining dispute.  Could you provide TAGs to support our numbers?\n\nUgh!  Hopefully this is it.\n\nJenny", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [64, 67, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "There will be two presentations tomorrow from UBS commencing at 2:30 p.m. (CST).  These will be held in ECS 06980 and the conference dial-in numbers are listed below.  \n\n\t\t\t\t2:30 p.m.\tBill Glass & Bill Bradford - Credit\n\t\t\t\t3:00 p.m.\tAlex Fusco - New Business Guidelines\n\nDial-in #\t\t800.486.2726\nHost code\t353763 (Louise)\nParticipant\t547763\n\nMany Thanks,\n\nLiz Taylor\nAssistant to Greg Whalley\n713.853.1935 office\n713.853.1838 fax\n713.854.3056 mobile", "labels": [[69, 72, "url"], [107, 114, "phone"], [46, 49, "ORG"], [184, 194, "PERSON"], [197, 219, "PERSON"], [234, 270, "PERSON"], [314, 320, "PERSON"], [356, 366, "PERSON"], [380, 393, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Hello Karen:\n\nI have returned to Houston after a trip to the East Coast: In Washington an=\nd New York I had the opportunity to further discuss and update the issue of=\n Argentina, and Latin America more broadly, with sources in both the financ=\nial and economic communities. =20\n\nHere is an overall update with some specifics highlighted:\n\nAs we had reported in July and August and as we discussed lat month, the ba=\nsic thesis still holds, at Treasury and the IFIs and in the emerging market=\n financial community: i.e.\n=20\nDifferentiation in DC and NY: Argentina is on its own and Brazil will be gi=\nven support, as will Turkey and Indonesia.  Policy since 9/11 relative to P=\nakistan has been indicative of the evolving Washington calculus; experience=\n of sustained weakness and unexpected shock of 9/11 has revealed that conta=\ngion is a secondary driver right now\nDifferentiation between BA and Sao Paulo: Decoupling of Brazilian Real and =\nC-Bond from Argy Peso NDFs and FRB in currency and bond markets continues t=\no strengthen the base policy bias of quarantine/reinforce relative to BA an=\nd SP, as has relative flight to quality in the EM asset class that has been=\n seen over the last few weeks, most notably in case of Mexico =20\nAnother waiting game vis-?-vis Argy: Despite the 'effective default' condit=\nions in Argy and a new spate of downgrades, the once again much rumored swa=\np/restructure is by no means a settled issue, and even if/once achieved sti=\nll leaves open the underlying problem of the peso-$ peg, w/ a dollarization=\n above parity scenario still lurking.  As with the saga all year, this is p=\nrimarily a political drama being conveyed through economic channels\nOil in the policy mix: Collapse and continuing pressure in oil market will =\nexpose and exacerbate underlying fault-lines both within OPEC and between O=\nPEC and non-OPEC producers: apart from obviously more visible Russian role,=\n this will continue build in a focus on regional players inside and outside=\n the cartel: Venezuela (including internal Chavez dynamic, Venezuela within=\n OPEC, and price v. market share debate) and Mexico, incl. relative to West=\nern Hemisphere supply security.  The end of the Congressional year in DC, w=\nar politics, and the upcoming OPEC meeting next week will continue to contr=\nibute near term volatility\nDomestic US politics: Current breakdown of post-9/11 bipartisan consensus n=\now in full throat as appropriations and special needs bills are facing prob=\nlems in committees, on the floors of both chambers and/or in the face of a =\nconferencing.  Of particular importance at this time is the Senate Finance =\nCommittee's consideration of a stimulus bill.  The lack of progress, despit=\ne an attempt late last week by the White House to bring more executive pres=\nsure to bear, has led to concern that a final stimulus bill may not be read=\ny until just before Christmas, and there remains a danger that no stimulus =\nbill will go through.  A new wrinkle in this drama is the effort by Alaskan=\n Sens. Stevens and Murkowski to potentially attach an energy bill, includin=\ng ANWR drilling, to any Senate stimulus bill, focusing on national security=\n interests in order to sway moderates.  Given that the markets have already=\n priced in a stimulus bill by around thanksgiving and on the order of $100B=\n, there is downside risk in delay or defeat.  These dangers have been heigh=\ntened further over the past week as weak data has come in even weaker than =\nexpected, putting a further premium on a sooner, more dramatic recovery\n\nLet me know if this is helpful and if there are any macroecon or political =\nspecifics that you are particularly concerned about.=20\n\n\nRegards,\nBrendan\nx54763", "labels": [[516, 519, "url"], [3721, 3726, "phone"], [6, 11, "PERSON"], [33, 40, "GPE"], [57, 71, "LOC"], [76, 86, "GPE"], [93, 101, "GPE"], [169, 178, "GPE"], [184, 197, "LOC"], [398, 407, "ORG"], [417, 420, "PERSON"], [444, 452, "ORG"], [544, 546, "GPE"], [551, 553, "GPE"], [555, 564, "GPE"], [583, 589, "GPE"], [602, 605, "ORG"], [623, 629, "GPE"], [634, 643, "GPE"], [679, 686, "PERSON"], [723, 733, "GPE"], [894, 896, "ORG"], [901, 910, "GPE"], [959, 968, "ORG"], [978, 981, "ORG"], [1094, 1096, "ORG"], [1103, 1105, "ORG"], [1233, 1239, "GPE"], [1275, 1279, "PERSON"], [1329, 1333, "ORG"], [1470, 1474, "PERSON"], [1831, 1835, "ORG"], [1848, 1851, "ORG"], [1851, 1854, "ORG"], [1863, 1867, "ORG"], [1996, 2004, "GPE"], [2018, 2027, "GPE"], [2048, 2054, "PERSON"], [2064, 2081, "PERSON"], [2083, 2087, "ORG"], [2127, 2133, "GPE"], [2135, 2139, "GPE"], [2159, 2173, "ORG"], [2229, 2231, "GPE"], [2266, 2270, "ORG"], [2349, 2351, "GPE"], [2488, 2493, "ORG"], [2631, 2637, "ORG"], [2756, 2771, "ORG"], [3040, 3047, "PERSON"], [3052, 3061, "PERSON"], [3134, 3140, "ORG"], [3177, 3186, "ORG"], [3255, 3263, "ORG"], [3712, 3719, "PERSON"], [3720, 3726, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Hi Lisa,\nThe counterparty is showing this deal but I am not and their deal numbers are different from ours. They supplied a tag number but it was not enough information so I have asked the counterparty for addition information and I will get back with you on this. Thanks.", "labels": [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I'm working on settlement issues for NVP, DMS 12398.  Can you provide me with a deal#?\n\nLisa", "labels": [[45, 51, "phone"], [37, 40, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Please see the attached documents.  Thank you.\n\nJoan McInnis\nPower Pool of Alberta\nAdministrative Assistant\nBus: (403)233-6400\nFax: (403)543-0388\ne-mail:joan.mcinnis@powerpool.ab.ca", "labels": [[146, 181, "email"], [153, 165, "url"], [113, 121, "phone"], [48, 60, "PERSON"], [61, 71, "ORG"], [75, 82, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Rick Carson asked me to forward this email to you.\n\nThanks,\n\nSharon", "labels": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [61, 67, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "\tAll Enron personnel currently allowed access to this room need to retain that access until, and unless, their employment with Enron is terminated.\n\tAny access restrictions, or additions, should still be cleared by myself or Bill Bradford, subject to the above limitations.\n\n\tPlease give me a call if you have further questions.\n\n\tThanks,\n\n\tDebbie", "labels": [[5, 10, "ORG"], [127, 132, "ORG"], [225, 238, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Please advise.\n\nThe most ability is responsibility.  Nothing happens until someone steps forward and says, \"You can count on me.\"\n \nHolly Strong\nSecurity System Coordinator\nEnron Corp\nBusiness Controls\nCell Phone 832-473-9867", "labels": [[212, 220, "phone"], [173, 184, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Thanks!", "labels": []}
{"text": "This should be completed by EOBToday\n\nThe most ability is responsibility.  Nothing happens until someone steps forward and says, \"You can count on me.\"\n \nHolly Strong\nSecurity System Coordinator\nEnron Corp\nBusiness Controls\nCell Phone 832-473-9867", "labels": [[234, 242, "phone"], [28, 36, "ORG"], [195, 206, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "I have one additional person who should have access.  Her name is Tanya Rohauer.\n\nThanks,\n\nSharon", "labels": [[66, 79, "PERSON"], [91, 97, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Hi Holly,\n\nWe have a request that must be done today - as soon as possible.  ECN 2886 is a fileroom that has restricted access.  For security purposes, as of today, only the following are allowed access:\n\nKortney Brown\nRick Carson\nVeronica Gonzalez\nDavid Gorte\nBjorn Hagelmann\nKaren Heathman\nRita Hennessey\nDonna Lowry\nTom Moran\nSharon Sullo\nJane Wilhite\n\nPlease call me as soon as possible to discuss when this security can be changed.  I will be happy to provide whatever information is necessary.\n\nI appreciate your help,\n\nSharon Sullo\nx31946\ncell 713-305-4883", "labels": [[80, 86, "phone"], [0, 8, "PERSON"], [205, 218, "PERSON"], [219, 230, "PERSON"], [231, 248, "PERSON"], [249, 260, "PERSON"], [261, 276, "PERSON"], [277, 291, "PERSON"], [292, 306, "PERSON"], [307, 318, "PERSON"], [319, 328, "PERSON"], [329, 341, "PERSON"], [342, 354, "PERSON"], [526, 539, "PERSON"], [539, 545, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Effective with the November 15 payday, electronic viewing and printing of your direct deposit advice will be available on eHRonline.  This new feature allows you to view your pay information at a time convenient for you.  Later this year, you will be able to view this information from your home on your ClickAtHome computer.\n\nThe following is information to help you view this document beginning on November 15.  To access and print your pay advice from eHRonline:\n\n  1.\tLog-on to eHRonline with your \"P\" number and password. \nFor more details on how to log-on to eHRonline, see \nstep-by-step instructions at \nhttp://isc.enron.com/site/doclibrary/user/\n  2.\tNavigate to the pay advice using the following navigation \nmenus:\n?\tPay Information\n?\tPaycheck Inquiry\n  3.\tSelect the appropriate payroll period.\n  4.\tClick on the Continue button.\n  5.\tClick on the payroll period link under the Period heading; \na new window opens.\n  6.\tSelect the Open this file from its current location option.\n  7.\tClick on the OK button; this starts Adobe Acrobat Reader.\n  8.\tView your pay advice.\n  9.\tClick on the Print icon from the main toolbar.\n10.\tVerify/change the displayed printer.\n11.\tClick on the OK button to print the pay advice at the \ndesignated printer.  For more details on how to view & print \nyour pay advice from eHRonline, see step-by-step \ninstructions at http://isc.enron.com/site/doclibrary/user/\n\nThe advice information will remain on this site throughout the year allowing you to view or print the information at your convenience.  You can view a sample of the online pay stub by following this link to http://hrweb.enron.com/, click on Payroll Services and then on Payroll Forms.\n\nIf you'd like more details, there will be an Information Booth on November 13 through 15 from 11 am to 2 pm in the lobby of Enron North.  Come by and visit with Payroll Representatives who will demonstrate how the process works.", "labels": [[611, 627, "url"], [824, 832, "ORG"], [1032, 1052, "ORG"], [1059, 1063, "ORG"], [1646, 1662, "ORG"], [1675, 1688, "ORG"], [1736, 1753, "ORG"], [1815, 1826, "ORG"], [1852, 1875, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Lisa,\n\nMark is the one that is taking care of that CP and he is not in today.Sabrina Minnis is original coordinator and I asked if she had copies of the information for Hafslund and she replied that she gave it information to Mark Confer.  I'll leave him a note letting him know what you need. The Hafslund issue that I was working with is dealing with the month of Jan 2001. Let me know if I could be of any more assistance to you.\n\nKa'Tina-", "labels": [[71, 84, "url"], [369, 374, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [7, 11, "PERSON"], [51, 53, "ORG"], [77, 91, "PERSON"], [169, 177, "GPE"], [226, 237, "PERSON"], [298, 306, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Both for all of Dec and or any day that has discrepancy.\nThanks!\n\nlisa", "labels": []}
{"text": "Lisa,\n\n\tDO you need the detail the Enron has for Hafslund or the detail from Hasfslund or Dec 01?\n\nKa'Tina", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [35, 40, "ORG"], [49, 57, "GPE"], [77, 86, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "I am on a conference call every morning at 10:00 am.  Let me bring this up tomorrow and see what they want to do.\n\nDanielle", "labels": [[42, 49, "phone"], [115, 123, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "who at UBS should we talk to?", "labels": [[7, 10, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "The contracts might have been from Calgary, I just don't know if anyone from Calgary is talking with the contracts group from UBS?\nDoes anyone know?\n\nDanielle", "labels": [[35, 42, "GPE"], [77, 84, "GPE"], [126, 129, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "1 user of accumap\n\n I'll look into the other issues, I just thought that you may know who may be handling it, we may just do it directly from Calgary", "labels": [[10, 17, "ORG"], [142, 149, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "John:\n\nI have not found anyone who was trying to renew these contracts.  I am meeting with IHS on Thursday so I will make sure we add Accumap.  How many user of Accumap will you need?  I will forward the cost to you prior to sending the contracts to UBS.  \n\nDo you know who managed the contracts with NOVA, Power Pool of Alberta, OASIS or ESBI so that I can gather contact information and begin the contract management of these applications.\n\nThanks,\n\nDanielle  ", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [91, 94, "ORG"], [134, 141, "PERSON"], [161, 168, "ORG"], [250, 253, "ORG"], [301, 305, "ORG"], [307, 317, "ORG"], [321, 328, "GPE"], [330, 335, "GPE"], [339, 343, "ORG"], [452, 460, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "I have no knowledge of anyone looking into the resources listed.\n\nChris", "labels": [[66, 71, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Chris / Lloyd:\n\nTo answer John's question do you know if anyone is looking into NOVA, Power Pool of Alberta, OASIS, or ESBI ? \n\nThanks,\n\nDanielle", "labels": [[0, 14, "PERSON"], [26, 30, "PERSON"], [80, 84, "ORG"], [100, 107, "GPE"], [109, 114, "GPE"], [119, 123, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Get Connected with e-Statements.\n\nSign up for Electronic Statements\nfrom Enron Federal Credit Union\nby November 15\nto be entered into a contest to win a\nPalm Vx!\n\nLog on to www.enronfcu.com to apply\nor for more information.", "labels": [[173, 189, "url"], [73, 99, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Danielle, in general we need everything that Houston gets in addition to the info that is listed as Calgary on your spreadsheet.  One information source in not listed on your sheet.\n\nIHS Accumap\t\tPriority 2\tContact: Carmen (403) 770-4503 phone, (403) 874-4218 cell\n\nCan you tell me if anyone in Houston is working on setting up accounts with NOVA, Power Pool of Alberta, OASIS, ESBI?  These are gas and power related entities that we have to have accounts with the schedule physical gas and electricity.", "labels": [[223, 232, "phone"], [0, 8, "ORG"], [45, 52, "GPE"], [100, 107, "GPE"], [183, 194, "ORG"], [216, 222, "PERSON"], [295, 302, "GPE"], [342, 346, "ORG"], [348, 358, "ORG"], [362, 369, "GPE"], [378, 382, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "John:\n\nHere are the contracts we are currently creating with UBS.  Please verify that we have not missed any applications/publications or subscriptions.  \n\nHighlight in Red the systems you will need and mark the priority from 1-5,  1 being critical.\n\n\nThank you,\n\nDanielle", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [61, 64, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Lisa,\n\n\tDO you need the detail the Enron has for Hafslund or the detail from Hasfslund or Dec 01?\n\nKa'Tina", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [35, 40, "ORG"], [49, 57, "GPE"], [77, 86, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Bryan, can you get me an answer on the discrepancies between dates identified in John's response to me below?\n\nThanks\nGreg", "labels": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [81, 85, "PERSON"], [118, 122, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "according to the packet that was distributed in the meeting today with BC, it appears that Calpine, El Paso, Williams, AEC Marketing, AEC Storage are all FEB 1, this doesn't jive with what you just sent, wassup?", "labels": [[71, 73, "ORG"], [91, 98, "ORG"], [100, 107, "GPE"], [109, 117, "GPE"], [119, 132, "ORG"], [134, 145, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Further to our meeting today, please find attached the list of contracts ECC is taking the view are properly terminated and the dates of such termination (in ECC's opinion).  This list was last updated on January 9, 2002 before I went away, so Bryan, if there are any other counterparties that should be added to the list, can you please let Kyle, Eric, John and myself know as soon as possible?\n\nThanks\nGreg", "labels": [[215, 221, "phone"], [158, 161, "ORG"], [244, 249, "PERSON"], [342, 346, "PERSON"], [348, 352, "PERSON"], [354, 358, "PERSON"], [404, 408, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Rick Buy had a conversation with Pug Winokur yesterday in which Pug requested that a change in the Transaction Approval Process be effected immediately so that all divestitures in excess of $50 million be presented to the Board for its approval.    This change means that this transaction will need to go the the Board.\n\nPlease let me know if you have any questions or comments.\n\nRegards,\n\nDave", "labels": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [33, 44, "PERSON"], [64, 67, "ORG"], [222, 227, "ORG"], [305, 318, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Ok by me as long as it agrees with our corp governance policies\n--------------------------\nsent from my blackberry address - jeffrey.mcmahon@skytel.com", "labels": [[125, 151, "email"], [125, 140, "url"]]}
{"text": "Dash was signed back in October and we determined that board approval was not needed.  Buy and Pug said that non-core assets less than $500 million did not need board approval.  The document has been signed and we do not have an out for our board.  \n--------------------------\nSent from my BlackBerry Wireless Handheld (www.BlackBerry.net)", "labels": [[320, 338, "url"], [95, 98, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "  <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/images/news/corps/199.gif>\n\nNewsBeat:Daily News 11/07/2001\n\n\n\nThis email is a daily service of Forestweb <http://www.forestweb.com>'s NewsBeat. \n\nAll the stories from Wednesday, Nov. 7, are available under Wednesday's Headlines. <http://www.forestweb.com/taf/yesterday.taf?dt=11/07/01> \n\nNewly posted on Forestweb: CIBC World Markets. Canada - U.S. Lumber Dispute, Where Do We Go From Here? Click CIBC  <http://www.forestweb.com/editorial/analyst/cibc/cibc.11.06.01.pdf>to download. \n\nIf this NewsBeat. was forwarded to you by a colleague, please respect our copyright and order your own subscription. Corporate rates are available. For more information email NewsBeat <mailto:newsbeat@forestweb.com> \n\n\nContents\n\n\nCanada paper output off 5% through 3Q as September drops 10% ( More <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#story15163>...) \n5 government agencies shift from snail mail to e-mail due to anthrax ( More <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#story15155>...) \nPace picks up in softwood dispute negotiations ( More <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#story15161>...) \nWeyerhaeuser gets dual certification on all Ore. and Wash. timberlands ( More <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#story15143>...) \nBombs planted against forest genetics program in Upper Michigan ( More <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#story15162>...) \nPotlatch extends holiday shutdowns at lumber, wood panel mills ( More <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#story15165>...) \nNorampac to acquire Star Corrugated Box of Maspeth, N.Y. ( More <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#story15138>...) \nWal-Mart dampening Procter & Gamble's diaper business ( More <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#story15131>...) \n\n\nCanada paper output off 5% through 3Q as September drops 10%\n\n11/07/2001 16:07:00, Forestweb \n\n\nSAN FRANCISCO, Nov. 7, 2001 (Forestweb) -- Canada's total paper and paperboard production is down 5% through the first nine months of the year as September production dropped 10% compared with a year ago, the Pulp and Paper Products Council in Montreal reported. ...\n( Story... <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15163&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926>) \t\n \t\ntop of page <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#top> \t\n  _____  \n\n\n\n5 government agencies shift from snail mail to e-mail due to anthrax\n\n11/07/2001 10:43:59, BW \n\n\nWASHINGTON, D.C., Nov. 7, 2001 (Business Wire/press release)-- Anthrax concerns have caused the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, the Federal Communication Commission, and the Departments of Labor, Interior, and Transportation to encourage Internet use instead of snail mail, according to NetCompliance, an Internet provider of \"paperless\" compliance solutions....\n( Story... <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15155&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926>) \t\n \t\ntop of page <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#top> \t\n  _____  \n\n\n\nPace picks up in softwood dispute negotiations\n\n11/07/2001 13:50:13, Forestweb \n\n\nBy Linda K. Barr, Forestweb \n\nPORT ORCHARD, Wash., Nov. 7, 2001 (Forestweb) -- In the aftermath of the antidumping ruling by the U.S. Department of Commerce, released on Oct.31, 2001, the pace o...\n( Story... <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15161&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926>) \n\n \t\ntop of page <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#top> \t\n  _____  \n\n\n\nWeyerhaeuser gets dual certification on all Ore. and Wash. timberlands\n\n11/07/2001 08:56:12, BW \n\n\nWeyerhaeuser Western U.S. Timberlands Achieves Environmental Certification \n\nOne of the World's Largest Single Blocks of Private Forest to be Certified \n\nFEDERAL WAY, Wash., Nov. 7, 2001 (Busines...\n( Story... <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15143&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926>) \n\n \t\ntop of page <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#top> \t\n  _____  \n\n\n\nBombs planted against forest genetics program in Upper Michigan\n\n11/07/2001 15:21:08, Forestweb \n\n\nBy James McLaren \n\nSAN FRANCISCO, Nov. 7, 2001 (Forestweb) -- Two explosive devices were removed without incident early Monday at Michigan Technological University in Houghton, Mich., and the sus...\n( Story... <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15162&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926>) \n\n \t\ntop of page <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#top> \t\n  _____  \n\n\n\nPotlatch extends holiday shutdowns at lumber, wood panel mills\n\n11/07/2001 16:49:35, BW \n\n\nSPOKANE, Wash., Nov. 7, 2001 (press release) -- A combination of factors, including extremely slow markets for lumber and panel products, will result in extended holiday shutdowns at three of Potlatch Corporation's (NYSE:PCH - news) Idaho lumber, plywood and particleboard mills and holiday shutdowns at its three Minnesota oriented strand board (OSB) mills. ...\n( Story... <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15165&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926>) \t\n \t\ntop of page <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#top> \t\n  _____  \n\n\n\nNorampac to acquire Star Corrugated Box of Maspeth, N.Y.\n\n11/07/2001 08:16:35, CNW \n\n\nMONTREAL, Nov. 7, 2001 (Canada NewsWire/press release)- Norampac Inc., through its wholly-owned subsidiary Norampac Holding US Inc., has entered into an agreement to acquire Star Corrugated Box Co. Inc. ( \"Star\" ). In business since 1906, Star operates a corrugated products converting plant with annual production of over 1 billion square feet....\n( Story... <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15138&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926>) \t\n \t\ntop of page <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#top> \t\n  _____  \n\n\n\nWal-Mart dampening Procter & Gamble's diaper business\n\n11/07/2001 06:53:22, Press Reports \n\n\nNov. 7, 2001 (press reports) -- Procter & Gamble is losing valuable market share to Wal-Mart's store brand diapers, according to a report in the December 2001 issue of Kiplinger's Personal Finance magazine....\n( Story... <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15131&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926>) \t\n \t\ntop of page <http://www.forestweb.com/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2070&_UserReference=53518CE48B18B4EF3BE96926#top> \t\n  _____  \n\n\n\nTo opt out of this newsletter or to make suggestions regarding NewsBeat, please email NewsBeat <mailto:pricebeat@forestweb.com>.\n\n\n\nAll news reports are copyrighted by the respective authors.\npowered by Forestweb", "labels": [[704, 734, "email"], [3, 35, "url"], [82, 88, "phone"], [339, 348, "ORG"], [350, 368, "ORG"], [370, 376, "GPE"], [384, 398, "ORG"], [432, 436, "GPE"], [528, 536, "ORG"], [750, 756, "GPE"], [1410, 1422, "ORG"], [1454, 1458, "GPE"], [1463, 1468, "GPE"], [1691, 1705, "LOC"], [1867, 1875, "PERSON"], [2091, 2099, "PERSON"], [2134, 2141, "GPE"], [2143, 2147, "GPE"], [2309, 2317, "ORG"], [2328, 2346, "ORG"], [2526, 2532, "GPE"], [2609, 2622, "ORG"], [2622, 2635, "GPE"], [2651, 2660, "ORG"], [2665, 2671, "GPE"], [2827, 2862, "ORG"], [2866, 2874, "GPE"], [3320, 3322, "ORG"], [3326, 3336, "GPE"], [3338, 3342, "GPE"], [3358, 3388, "ORG"], [3418, 3458, "ORG"], [3460, 3496, "ORG"], [3506, 3526, "ORG"], [3528, 3536, "ORG"], [3542, 3556, "ORG"], [3619, 3632, "ORG"], [4104, 4113, "ORG"], [4120, 4133, "PERSON"], [4135, 4144, "ORG"], [4152, 4159, "GPE"], [4161, 4166, "GPE"], [4182, 4191, "ORG"], [4242, 4273, "ORG"], [4655, 4667, "ORG"], [4699, 4703, "GPE"], [4708, 4713, "GPE"], [4754, 4828, "ORG"], [4921, 4926, "GPE"], [5342, 5356, "GPE"], [5379, 5392, "ORG"], [5395, 5408, "PERSON"], [5411, 5424, "GPE"], [5440, 5449, "ORG"], [5522, 5555, "ORG"], [5559, 5567, "GPE"], [5569, 5574, "GPE"], [5931, 5939, "PERSON"], [6016, 6022, "ORG"], [6022, 6029, "GPE"], [6031, 6036, "GPE"], [6214, 6236, "ORG"], [6238, 6242, "ORG"], [6243, 6253, "ORG"], [6255, 6260, "GPE"], [6336, 6345, "GPE"], [6369, 6372, "PERSON"], [6725, 6733, "PERSON"], [6768, 6775, "GPE"], [6777, 6781, "GPE"], [6804, 6811, "ORG"], [6811, 6819, "GPE"], [6835, 6856, "ORG"], [6867, 6880, "ORG"], [6918, 6942, "ORG"], [6985, 7013, "ORG"], [7050, 7054, "ORG"], [7500, 7508, "ORG"], [7519, 7537, "ORG"], [7625, 7641, "ORG"], [7677, 7687, "ORG"], [7761, 7789, "ORG"], [8206, 8214, "ORG"], [8346, 8355, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Katina,\n\nCould you please get together with Lisa and get her what she needs.  I think it might relate to that ECAR/Allegheny stuff you were working on the other day.\n\nRebecca", "labels": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [44, 48, "PERSON"], [110, 114, "ORG"], [115, 124, "GPE"], [167, 174, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I'm working on a settlement issue with subject counterparty for December.  The unique id is 12596.  Can you send me Hafslund's detailed data for Dec 1?  \n\nLisa ", "labels": [[91, 97, "phone"], [116, 124, "GPE"], [155, 159, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Further to our meeting today, please find attached the list of contracts ECC is taking the view are properly terminated and the dates of such termination (in ECC's opinion).  This list was last updated on January 9, 2002 before I went away, so Bryan, if there are any other counterparties that should be added to the list, can you please let Kyle, Eric, John and myself know as soon as possible?\n\nThanks\nGreg", "labels": [[215, 221, "phone"], [158, 161, "ORG"], [244, 249, "PERSON"], [342, 346, "PERSON"], [348, 352, "PERSON"], [354, 358, "PERSON"], [404, 408, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "I would see the primary responsibilities:\n\n\n1. Develop with Fallon a written process for the valuation of terminated contracts.  We will most likely only have Bjorn for a short period of time given his reluctance to go to NETCO.  While no one appears to care about the fact that we have no way to render a correct value for financial statement purposes, this would be a priority if I was managing the estate.   There is no metric for the approval of comprises internally.  Our curves say one value, the counterparties quotes say another.  Differences in value may be a better metric that notional settlement amounts.\n2. With IT, assure that the terminated contracts are frozen in value.   The book is currently floating, rendering an open position which is unmeasured as to VaR.  Examine ways, if any, to manage this uncovered market risk. \n3. Valuation of assets held for sale and DASH process.   It would appear that we should work backwards from the summary of sale that the Unsecured Creditors Committee wants.   There have already been complaints about multiple forms (DASH, transaction review committee for).  This would require revamping the DASH process and TAP.   \n4. Revaluation of International assets.\n5. To the extent EES performs post petition, value this book and the associated  ongoing costs associated with it.\n6. My understanding is that the billing on performing accounts is behind. Manage and develop a process to collect these past due amounts.  Collectibility does not improve with time.\n7. Ongoing review of business unit's cash requests.\n8. Develop a systematized IT solution to payments and transfers made 90 days prior to bankruptcy (in process).\n9. Manage the bankrupt counterparty portfolio.\n10. Collect amounts owed by PG&E and So Cal Edison ($545 million notional).\n11. Maintain a pipeline report.", "labels": [[60, 66, "ORG"], [222, 227, "PERSON"], [974, 1007, "ORG"], [1149, 1153, "ORG"], [1166, 1169, "ORG"], [1177, 1205, "ORG"], [1231, 1234, "ORG"], [1749, 1753, "ORG"], [1761, 1771, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "We are hoping to be able to begin using OATI certificates by the end of this \nweek or early next week.  At some point, I will notify you of a default \npassword to use for your first login.  You will be expected to replace the \ndefault with your own password on your first login. However, before we can \nimplement, I need updated information from you.    Please reply to this \nmessage with the following information.\n\n1.\tUser name\n\n2.\tEmail address\n\n3.\tPhone number\n\n4.\tDo you currently have an OATI digital certificate?\n\n5.\tI you have an OATI certificate, what is the common name?\n\n6.\tIf you do not have an OATI certificate, what is the name of your Security \nOfficer or security contact?\n\nI am not certain at this point whether we can use Tradewave and OATI \ncertificates in parallel.  It seems to be a good possibility, but hasn't yet been \nconfirmed.  If we are able to do so, we have until the end of June to complete \neveryone's conversion.  If not, we will have to pick a date certain for the \nchange.  Since I will be on the road from June 25-28, the changeover date \nwould have to be no later than June 24.\n\nThe attached file describes how to obtain a certificate from OATI.", "labels": [[1046, 1052, "phone"], [40, 44, "ORG"], [494, 498, "ORG"], [607, 611, "ORG"], [740, 749, "ORG"], [754, 758, "ORG"], [1177, 1181, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "With the filing of the Hart-Scott-Rodino application last week, it looks like our updated launch timeline is as follows. Note that it is still possible that this timeline could shift:\n\nWeek of Jan 28:\n\nWe will distribute a packet to each of the Originators/Traders who have volounteered to call customers and assist in getting signed Password Applications. The packets will contain:\n\nKey Messages\nFrequently Asked Questions (FAQs)\nTop Counterparty Checklist \nExternal Customer Cover Letter\nPassword Application (PA)\nRegistration Form\nFax Cover Sheet for PA/Registration \nElectronic Trading Agreement (ETA)\nInternal online Marketing Contact List\n\nEach person receiving a pack will contact the Master Users at the companies they have volounteered for and send them copies of the Password Application (PA) and Electronic Trading Agreement (ETA). During this week, we will be working hard to get as many of the PA's returned as possible. Once we have a signed PA, we can send the customer their new User ID, which will allow them to start trading on the day we launch the new site.\n\nA Splash page will be available at www.UBSWenergy.com or via an automatic redirect from www.enrononline.com. This page will tell customers about the pending launch of www.UBSWenergy.com and provide links to the PA and Registration screens and also to the User Admin screens, which will allow customer Master Users to start setting up their Sub Users.\n\nThe Splash page will look something like the following:\n\n \n\n\nWeek of Feb. 4:\n\nWe will send out a mass mailing to approx. 3,000 individuals at 450 companies inviting them to sign up for the site. Included in the package will be a simple brochure, copies of the PA and ETA, key messages and a list of Frequently Asked Questions.\n\nWeek of Feb. 11:\n\nThe site will launch, with at least financial products (timing for gas physical and power physical to be determined according to regulatory issues). \n\nGeneral Terms and Conditions (GTC's) will be available online and must be accepted online before a company can start to trade a particular commodity.\n\t\t\n\nTrading/Origination Coordination\n\nThe Top 50 customers will have at least an initial contact within the first two days of starting the marketing effort and that all customers who previously traded either gas or power will receive a mailing within the first 10 days. An online marketer has been assigned as coordinator for each company and will assist each Trader/Originator in following up with Master Users as necessary to make sure PA's are signed and returned.\n\n\nUBSWenergy Marketing Contacts:\n\nFor Marketing-specific questions, please use the following contacts. For other questions, please contact Bob Shults (30397) or Dave Forster (31861).\t\t\n\nTeresa Mandola (39807) - Power\nJennifer McQuade (53614) - Power\nDan Diamond (39673) - Gas\n\n\n<Embedded Picture (Metafile)>", "labels": [[1114, 1132, "url"], [2696, 2703, "phone"], [334, 355, "PERSON"], [459, 489, "ORG"], [601, 604, "ORG"], [837, 840, "ORG"], [907, 909, "ORG"], [956, 958, "ORG"], [1000, 1002, "ORG"], [1081, 1087, "ORG"], [1114, 1132, "ORG"], [1246, 1264, "ORG"], [1286, 1309, "ORG"], [1435, 1441, "ORG"], [1691, 1693, "ORG"], [1698, 1701, "ORG"], [1958, 1961, "ORG"], [2438, 2455, "ORG"], [2548, 2577, "ORG"], [2685, 2695, "PERSON"], [2707, 2719, "PERSON"], [2732, 2746, "PERSON"], [2763, 2779, "PERSON"], [2796, 2807, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "The following reports have been waiting for your approval for more than 4 days.  Please review.\n\nOwner: Karen K Heathman\nReport Name: Brad Larson\nDays In Mgr. Queue: 7", "labels": [[104, 121, "PERSON"], [134, 145, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Julie-\n\n  The following City of Riverside deals have been marked to the W. Non-Performance book as of June 7, 2002 and should not be scheduled:\n\n  580382 \n  897695\n  517664\n  591087\n \n  Let me know id you have any questions.\n\n  Virginia", "labels": [[109, 115, "phone"], [24, 41, "GPE"], [228, 236, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Please disregard the Hydro slide (p.12 or 13) in the Presentation.  I have added a hydro tab in the quick info spreadsheet.", "labels": [[36, 45, "phone"], [21, 26, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Enron and Dynegy each announced today that they are holding discussions about a possible merger of the two companies.  As you know, Dynegy is a major player in the energy marketplace, and is not only a competitor, but also a counterparty of Enron.  This is just one of several options that we are considering.\n\nUpon receipt of this announcement, the NYSE briefly suspended trading of both Enron and Dynegy.  We have no additional information we can share at this time.  We'll keep you updated as developments occur.", "labels": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [10, 16, "PERSON"], [132, 138, "PERSON"], [241, 246, "ORG"], [350, 354, "ORG"], [389, 394, "ORG"], [399, 405, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "To continue getting familiar with Ontario, please review the document OEFC_demandSupp_UBS.ppt on your I:/common/OEFC directory.  It is a presentation we gave to OEFC in the fall.\n\nHere is a spreadsheet with additional information.\n\n \nSome intertie information may vary from source to source.  This is due to the IMO's regular small adjustments to the capacity numbers.\n\nGT", "labels": [[86, 93, "url"], [34, 41, "ORG"], [112, 116, "ORG"], [161, 165, "ORG"], [312, 315, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "This presentation includes a synopsis of the assets that are in each of the major off-balance sheet vehicles which may be valuable going forward.", "labels": []}
{"text": "Per Barry Schnapper's request I have attached a copy of the Creditor Committee Presentation...\n\nDavid", "labels": [[4, 21, "PERSON"], [56, 91, "ORG"], [96, 101, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Ok we will charge you for 50 mw's on that day Thanks\n\nJohn Paulsen G4220\nWestern Area Power DSW\nPower Scheduling\nPaulsen@WAPA.GOV\n602-352-2557\n\n>>> \"Gang, Lisa\" <Lisa.Gang@ENRON.com> 06/06/02 09:37AM >>>\nEverything looks great except for May 28th.  We had 2 hours of 25MW of\ntxm.  It is supported under Tag #530 for your info.\n\nThanks \n\nLisa  ", "labels": [[121, 129, "url"], [68, 72, "phone"], [54, 72, "PERSON"], [73, 91, "ORG"], [92, 95, "ORG"], [337, 341, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": " - Enron Security Calculation 2002.xls ", "labels": [[30, 38, "url"], [29, 34, "phone"]]}
{"text": "Rick,\n\nDave asked me to send you the attached file to use as a starting point for the \"RAC's Roles\" project that you mentioned in the meeting.  This presentation was prepared a few weeks ago.\n\nThanks,\n\nSharon\nx31946", "labels": [[210, 215, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [7, 11, "PERSON"], [87, 90, "ORG"], [202, 208, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Portland Employees-\n\nAt this time Enron Portland has 5 parking spots allocated based on floor space and number of employees.  As UBS employees leave we do not automatically have the ability to take over their spots.  However, in renegotiating our lease with PGE we will address the possibility of taking over more that the 5 allocated spots.  We will keep you updated as to the progress of this.  For now, Khymberly Booth is checking into the availability of 1 or more of our spots and will offer any available spots to Portland employees based on Portland office seniority.  We will contact you individually if a spot becomes available.  If you have any questions please contact Kathy Sheppard or Khymberly Booth.\n\nThanks-\nKhymberly Booth", "labels": [[0, 8, "GPE"], [34, 39, "ORG"], [40, 48, "GPE"], [129, 132, "ORG"], [258, 261, "ORG"], [406, 421, "LOC"], [520, 528, "GPE"], [548, 556, "GPE"], [680, 694, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Rick, \n\nCommittee staff attendees included David L. Cavicke (Committee Majority Counsel), Brian McCullough (Committee Majority Professional Staff Member), Christopher Knauer (Committee Minority Investigator), and Michael Geffroy (Committee Minority Counsel).  \n\nJim ", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [43, 59, "PERSON"], [71, 87, "ORG"], [90, 106, "PERSON"], [155, 173, "PERSON"], [213, 228, "PERSON"], [262, 265, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Pulpex Bulletin for Thursday, November 8, 2001\n\nMarket News:\n             Bid      Ask     Last     High      Low   Vol    OI\nNBSK ------------------------------------------------------------\nNov01     411.00   423.00        -        -        -     -    80\nDec01     418.00   427.00        -        -        -     -   113\nJan02     423.00   432.00        -        -        -     -    41\nMar02     426.00   448.00        -        -        -     -   153\nJun02     449.00   469.00        -        -        -     -    40\nSep02     470.00   481.00        -        -        -     -    35\nDec02     480.00   497.00        -        -        -     -    15\nMar03     490.00        -        -        -        -     -     -\n\nBEK -------------------------------------------------------------\nNov01          -        -        -        -        -     -    26\nDec01          -        -        -        -        -     -    30\nJan02          -        -        -        -        -     -     -\nMar02          -        -        -        -        -     -     -\n\nSettlement Prices Futures\n          Today      Chg      Prev\nNBSK -------------------------------\nNov01    417.00     +6.00    411.00\nDec01    422.50     +4.50    418.00\nJan02    427.50     +2.50    425.00\nMar02    437.00     -2.50    439.50\nJun02    459.00     -1.50    460.50\nSep02    475.50     +0.00    475.50\nDec02    488.50     +0.00    488.50\nMar03    503.50     +0.00    503.50\n\nBEK --------------------------------\nNov01    404.00     +0.00    404.00\nDec01    407.00     +0.00    407.00\nJan02    414.00     +0.00    414.00\nMar02    421.00     +0.00    421.00\n\nThe above tables should ideally be viewed using Courier or other fixed fonts.\nDuring Pulpex opening hours (0830-1600 UK Time, 0930-1700 CET),prices\nare distributed on our web page: http://www.pulpex.com\n\nIf you would like someone else to receive this bulletin or to cancel your own\nplease mail: info@pulpex.com or fax: +44 20 7065 8941", "labels": [[1904, 1919, "email"], [1790, 1811, "url"], [41, 46, "phone"], [48, 59, "ORG"], [126, 130, "ORG"], [974, 979, "ORG"], [1101, 1105, "ORG"], [1427, 1430, "ORG"], [1657, 1664, "ORG"], [1694, 1700, "ORG"], [1726, 1728, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Please reply to confirm totals\n\nJohn Paulsen G4220\nWestern Area Power DSW\nPower Scheduling\nPaulsen@WAPA.GOV\n602-352-2557", "labels": [[99, 107, "url"], [46, 50, "phone"], [32, 50, "PERSON"], [51, 69, "ORG"], [70, 73, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Rob,\n\nMarkets\nMy marks show how we believe the market would trade if the market were open today, considering neighboring markets, transmission/wheeling costs, and fuel costs.  More of a expected liquidation value vs. the current Ontario market players bids and offers.\n\nThe market on 3yr 7x24 is being shown by a broker: $46-$48, and on the wholesale side I doubt the bid is actually there, or if so it is only a piece deep (50MW).  \n\nAs a result, I would show an actually two way of $43-$47.50 and be coming from the sell side to the industrial customers who may pay in the $46-$47 range.\n\nPeak, my 3yr mark is $52, but given the often bullish nature of new markets, I would be a bid for this summer and then look to offer the 3yr in the low fifties.  Upcoming changes in the Ontario system (Nodal vs. Zonal pricing) would have an effect on these term deals.\n\n\nStaffing and Services\n\nTrading\nOn the trading side, I will need to rehire personnel for the roles we laid off (an analyst and a temp IT programmer for fundies development).  Analyst wise, I am interested in bringing Brian Loy back if he is still available.  He has a good knowledge of the NUG contracts and is a good fit for a trading desk.  As our need for providing IMO Energy and Operating Reserve Services (bidding for specific NUGS and Dispatchable Loads) grows, it may be a good idea to bring Heather Mcillmurray over from the settlements group.  I have had initial discussions with Richard Crouch, Paul Devries and Heather on this matter.\n\nOrigination\nThis is your area of expertise. I would suggest two originators and an analyst.  If Dan Dorland is staying, he could continue on the origination side providing education to our new origination team, and being the analyst to assist the OEFC-NUG point personnel (Brian Loy's previous role).  \n\nIT\nImplementing the trading and VMS systems is a very important issue where timing will become an issue. I would suggest a short term (6mo) contract with Mike Marryott to manage the system's side of this process and to integrate with the Estate and NETCO on trading and settlements systems (specifically David Posten's VMS team).  His location should be in Toronto.  \n\nLet's get on these issues as soon as possible.\n\nOn specific personnel, I would have liked to have retained Jeff Borg and Chris Gaffney. \n\nOffice Space\nTembec, our neighbor on this floor, has often indicated that they are interested in some of our office space. If that interest remains, we could examine leasing all of the space passed the flat screens (the origination desk/pod, one conference room and storage area, not to include our server room).  This would leave us with space for up to 24 people, two conference rooms, & kitchen.  As an alternative, we could consider moving upstairs into the Enron Direct location.\n\nPotential Conflict of Interest\nI would suggest releasing employees that will not be part of Estate or UBS relatively soon.  Specifically, the group that is leaving here, but will be participating in the Ontario market.  UBS Ontario information and resources are proprietary and confidential.  If personnel are being kept on to wind-down specific activities, their access to UBS power & gas curves should be restricted.\n\nAs time becomes available, we should get together and discuss Ontario's business plan. \n\nThank you\nGarrett", "labels": [[322, 328, "phone"], [229, 236, "GPE"], [777, 784, "GPE"], [1078, 1087, "PERSON"], [1151, 1154, "ORG"], [1230, 1271, "ORG"], [1294, 1298, "ORG"], [1303, 1321, "PERSON"], [1361, 1380, "PERSON"], [1451, 1465, "PERSON"], [1467, 1479, "PERSON"], [1484, 1491, "PERSON"], [1605, 1616, "PERSON"], [1756, 1760, "ORG"], [1782, 1793, "PERSON"], [1845, 1848, "ORG"], [1967, 1980, "PERSON"], [2051, 2057, "ORG"], [2117, 2131, "PERSON"], [2132, 2135, "ORG"], [2170, 2177, "GPE"], [2289, 2298, "PERSON"], [2303, 2316, "PERSON"], [2333, 2339, "PERSON"], [2782, 2794, "ORG"], [2898, 2904, "ORG"], [2908, 2911, "ORG"], [3009, 3016, "GPE"], [3026, 3037, "ORG"], [3180, 3183, "ORG"], [3288, 3295, "GPE"], [3325, 3332, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Garrett, I take that these are your mids. Where would your 3yr two-way be?", "labels": [[0, 7, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "CAD\tPeak\t\t7x24\n1yr\t$50.00\t\t$42.75\n3yr\t$52.00\t\t$44.00\n5yr\t$52.50\t\t$44.00", "labels": [[20, 25, "phone"], [0, 3, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Conferring with Gorte, we need a new DASH for the India sale due to \n1) the time since signing (5 months)\n2) downward change in purchase price\n3) general change in circumstances of Enron\n \nIn addition to updating the numbers (as we discussed this morning), we should include\nan ownership structure diagram and a legal risk memo concerning what bankruptcy \nrelated approvals are required (if any).\n \nWhether or not Board approval is required is possibly an open issue. We will research.   ", "labels": [[16, 21, "PERSON"], [50, 55, "GPE"], [181, 186, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Lisa:\n\nIn the message below, Settlements in Houston is confirming that we have the correct understanding of the dispute concerning BPA in Dec. 01 (see the e-mail and spreadsheet I copied to you on May 30).  Let me know if you have questions as you research it.  \n\nAlso, do you need anything else from Settlements to enable you to work on the Hafslund request (see my email from May 29).\n\nNote - I am out of the office until Monday.\n\nHave a good weekend.  Jenny", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [44, 51, "GPE"], [131, 134, "ORG"], [301, 312, "ORG"], [342, 350, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Jennifer,\nYes, I do believe you have the correct understanding.  The ttls you have tie to the dms impact. Let me know if you have any questions.\n\nThanks,\nElsie", "labels": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [154, 159, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Elsie:\n\nSorry, in looking over this again with Lisa, we want to be sure that we understand the request correctly.  \n\nSee attached for my understanding of what you are requesting and please confirm.\n\nI looked at this from the perspective of each entire deal.  For each, I took the total price and volume of the deal and subtracted/added the MWs you specified and then calculated the revised value of each deal.  \n\nIs this a correct understanding of the changes needed and their impact?\n\nThanks, Jenny\n\n << File: 12593 - BPA.xls >> ", "labels": [[519, 526, "url"], [510, 517, "phone"], [0, 5, "PERSON"], [47, 51, "PERSON"], [494, 499, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Hey Jennifer,\n\tDid you have any more questions related to this?\nThanks,\nElsie\n713-853-6757", "labels": [[78, 85, "phone"], [4, 12, "PERSON"], [72, 77, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Dear Team,\n\nAttached is the updated price forecast.  This has RISI forecasts for each commodity.\n\nIf you have any questions, please call me.\n\nThanks,\n\nStacey\nStacey L. Wales\n\nStacey Wales\nOrigination Transaction Support\nEnron Industrial Markets\n713-345-7186", "labels": [[245, 252, "phone"], [62, 66, "ORG"], [151, 157, "PERSON"], [158, 173, "PERSON"], [175, 187, "PERSON"], [220, 245, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Got it, thanks.", "labels": []}
{"text": "Jennifer,,,,,I updated the dms....in the comment section this is for 2 deals...the difference between enpwer mw and revised mw will be 8150 mw (12600mw revised to 4450mw)...the spreadsheet is the detail for the changes needed and not totals for the deals.  \n\nThanks,\nElsie", "labels": [[134, 140, "phone"], [102, 111, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Elsie:\n\nThanks for the welcome!\n\nAlready I have a quick question - in the attached spreadsheet, the disputed MW columns seem to add up to 12600 and 4450.  In reading the DMS, I would expect them to add up to 14600 and 5600 (or 12600 and 3600, if I only include the referrenced deal, #12593). Am I missing something?\n\nJenny", "labels": [[137, 144, "phone"], [0, 5, "PERSON"], [170, 173, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "....and welcome aboard!", "labels": []}
{"text": " << File: to portland for bpa.xls >> \nHello,,,,,this is the support of the chgs needed for dms request 12593.  If you have questions or need additional info, I'm at 713-853-6757.\n\nThanks,\nElsie", "labels": [[26, 33, "url"], [102, 108, "phone"], [13, 21, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "This email is acknowledgement from the Power Pool of Alberta of the change\nin direct sales/forward contract registration for contracts that are\ncurrently registered with the Power Pool between Chevron Canada Resources\nand Enron Canada Power Corporation for trading after December 29 HE 1 2001.\nOn January 4 the Power Pool received your acknowledgement of Enron's change\nin the source asset for the direct sales/forward contract registrations for\ncontract # 1947 to modify the source from the Sundance 3 unit (SD3) to\nEnron's unmetered source asset (ECP-).  The modified registration terms will\nbe effective December 29 HE 1 2001 and will apply until the expiry date of\nthe contract registration for net settlement purposes.\n\nAs for the sink asset related to direct sales/forward contract # 1947, Enron\nhas acknowledged and accepted your change to the sink asset from CH1A to\nCH1U.  This change will be effective January 1, 2002 HE 1 and our systems\nwill be changed today.\n\nIf you have any questions relating to this matter, please give me a call.\n\nCarol Moline\nFinancial Controller\nPower Pool of Alberta\n(403) 233-4686\ncarol.moline@powerpool.ab.ca", "labels": [[1119, 1147, "email"], [1119, 1131, "url"], [287, 292, "phone"], [53, 60, "GPE"], [170, 184, "ORG"], [193, 218, "ORG"], [222, 252, "ORG"], [307, 321, "ORG"], [355, 360, "ORG"], [492, 502, "ORG"], [509, 512, "ORG"], [517, 522, "ORG"], [796, 801, "ORG"], [867, 871, "ORG"], [1048, 1061, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Please see attached.\n\nThanks.\nDonna", "labels": [[30, 35, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Lisa;\n\ncontact me with questions, this is just an idea of what is on Half.com and eBay.com.\nThe entire link is not highlighted on either link.  You need to copy and paste ot all, or redo your search.\n\nenough is enough...\n\nCheri\n\n\n\nhttp://search.ebay.com/search/search.dll?MfcISAPICommand=GetResult&ht=1&\nSortProperty=MetaEndSort&ebaytag1code=0&query=LSAT\n\nhttp://half.ebay.com/search/search.jsp?nthTime=1&product=books&keyword=LSAT&\nx=17\n\nThank you;\nCheri Thomas\nTransmission & Energy Services\n503.464-5078\n503.464-8178, fax\n503.803.1885, cell\nE-mail: \"Cheri_thomas@pgn.com\"\n\n3WTC-0506\n121 SW Salmon Street\nPortland, Oregon  97204", "labels": [[553, 573, "email"], [69, 77, "url"], [494, 501, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [222, 231, "PERSON"], [350, 354, "ORG"], [450, 462, "PERSON"], [607, 615, "GPE"], [617, 623, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Hi John,\n\n     As per our conversation last week, I just wanted to double check on a potential raise before the deal closes on Friday. I know that more than a few non-promotional raises have been offered and accepted for the transfer to UBS, and I'd like to make absolutely sure that I'm not eligible for one. As Cowan says, potentially the bonus pool may be much bigger next year, which is great, but it's not for sure. And given the promises Enron has dolled out over the years, it doesn't mean that much right now, especially considering it's in UBS's best interest for us not to make a killing in the first year in order to buy out the company at a lower price.\n\nThanks,\nRyan", "labels": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [237, 240, "ORG"], [313, 318, "PERSON"], [444, 449, "ORG"], [549, 552, "ORG"], [675, 679, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Lisa,\n\nPlease complete the attached file as discussed over the phone.\n\n- Frank, OATI ", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "<HTML>\n<HEAD>\n\t<TITLE>PULP, WRITING &amp; PRINTING PAPER 11/08/2001</TITLE>\n<base href=\"http://www.forestweb.com\">\n</HEAD>\n<BODY  TOPMARGIN=\"0\" LEFTMARGIN=\"20\" MARGINHEIGHT=\"0\" \nMARGINWIDTH=\"0\" BGCOLOR=\"#ffffff\">\n<a name=top></a><img src=\"http://www.forestweb.com/digest/images/news/corps/197.gif\">\n\n<h4>PULP, WRITING &amp; PRINTING PAPER 11/08/2001</h4><br clear=all>\n<DIV align=center>\n<p><table width=\"100%\" border=\"3\" cellspacing=\"0\" cellpadding=\"10\">\n  <tr>\n    <td>\n      <p><b><font face=\"Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif\" size=\"-1\" color=\"#000033\">Welcome</font></b><font face=\"Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif\" size=\"-1\"> \n        to Enron's Pulp, Writing &amp; Printing Paper News Service. This daily \n        mailing brings the most recent news headlines right to your inbox. You \n        may also receive this daily service specific to the following areas: 1) \n        Recovered, Container &amp; Packaging; 2) Newsprint; 3) Lumber. To join \n        any of these lists, <a href=\"http://www.forestweb.com/fwsnippets/mailinglists/enron_lists.html\"> \n        CLICK HERE</a>.</font></p>\n      <p><font face=\"Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif\" size=\"-1\">If you have any comments \n        or feedback, simply reply to this email. If you would like to unsubscribe \n        to the Pulp, Writing &amp; Printing Paper News service, please scroll \n        to the bottom of this email for instruction.</font></p>\n      <p><font face=\"Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif\" size=\"-1\">Thanks and enjoy.</font></p>\n    </td>\n  </tr>\n</table>\n </p>\n</DIV>\n<h4>Contents</h4>\n<TABLE WIDTH=\"600\" BORDER=\"0\" CELLPADDING=\"0\" CELLSPACING=\"0\">\n <TR VALIGN=TOP>\n<TD>\n<OL>\n<li>\nWeyerhaeuser names new manager at Cosmopolis, Wash., pulp mill\n   ( <A href=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#story15153\">More</a>...)</li>\n<li>\nCanada paper output off 5% through 3Q as September drops 10%   ( <A href=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#story15163\">More</a>...)</li>\n<li>\nBrascan's forest products operations contribute to 3Q earnings decline   ( <A href=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#story15168\">More</a>...)</li>\n<li>\nDomtar shutting 3 sawmills, 30 MMBF,  due to drop in demand, prices   ( <A href=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#story15170\">More</a>...)</li>\n<li>\nVotorantim, K-C de Mexico  among JPMorgan's top Latin American picks   ( <A href=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#story15176\">More</a>...)</li>\n<li>\nMunksjo reports paper earnings stable, big drop for pulp   ( <A href=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#story15177\">More</a>...)</li>\n</OL>\n</TD>\n</TR>\n</TABLE>\n<p><a name=\"story15153\"></a>\n<TABLE WIDTH=\"600\" BORDER=\"0\" CELLPADDING=\"0\" CELLSPACING=\"0\">\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n<TD>\n<h3>Weyerhaeuser names new manager at Cosmopolis, Wash., pulp mill\n</H3>\n<i>11/07/2001 10:36:15, Press Release</i>\n<br><br></TD>\n</TR>\n\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n\t<TD>\nCOSMOPOLIS, Wash., Nov. 5, 2001 (press release) -- Weyerhaeuser Co. today\n    announced that Fred Cassidy, has been named vice president and mill manager of\n    the Cosmopolis, Wash., pulp mill, effective immediately. Cassidy was formerly site\n    manager of the company?s North Bend, Ore., containerboard mill.\n\n    In his new role, Cassidy will focus on accelerating the mill?s performance\n    improvement efforts....<br>\n(<A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15153&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47\">Story...</a>)\n\n</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT>&nbsp;</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT><A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#top\"><IMG SRC=\"http://www.forestweb.com/digest/images/news/top.gif\" align=right WIDTH=\"56\" HEIGHT=\"12\"   \nBORDER=\"0\" ALT=\"top of page\"></A> \n</TD></TR>\n</TABLE>\n<HR>\n<p><a name=\"story15163\"></a>\n<TABLE WIDTH=\"600\" BORDER=\"0\" CELLPADDING=\"0\" CELLSPACING=\"0\">\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n<TD>\n<h3>Canada paper output off 5% through 3Q as September drops 10%</H3>\n<i>11/07/2001 16:07:00, Forestweb</i>\n<br><br></TD>\n</TR>\n\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n\t<TD>\n\n\n\nSAN FRANCISCO, Nov. 7, 2001 (Forestweb) -- Canada's total paper and paperboard production is down 5% through the first nine months of the year as September production dropped 10% compared with a year ago, the Pulp and Paper Products Council in Montreal reported. \n...<br>\n(<A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15163&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47\">Story...</a>)\n\n</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT>&nbsp;</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT><A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#top\"><IMG SRC=\"http://www.forestweb.com/digest/images/news/top.gif\" align=right WIDTH=\"56\" HEIGHT=\"12\"   \nBORDER=\"0\" ALT=\"top of page\"></A> \n</TD></TR>\n</TABLE>\n<HR>\n<p><a name=\"story15168\"></a>\n<TABLE WIDTH=\"600\" BORDER=\"0\" CELLPADDING=\"0\" CELLSPACING=\"0\">\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n<TD>\n<h3>Brascan's forest products operations contribute to 3Q earnings decline</H3>\n<i>11/08/2001 05:39:07, BW</i>\n<br><br></TD>\n</TR>\n\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n\t<TD>\nTORONTO, Nov. 8, 2001 (press release) -- Brascan Corporation today\nannounced income from continuing operations for the nine months ended\nSeptember 30, 2001 of $266 million or $1.35 per share, down from $297\nmillion or $1.51 per share in the same period of 2000. Total income\nfor the first nine months of 2000 was $557 million, which included\ngains of $260 million.\n...<br>\n(<A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15168&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47\">Story...</a>)\n\n</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT>&nbsp;</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT><A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#top\"><IMG SRC=\"http://www.forestweb.com/digest/images/news/top.gif\" align=right WIDTH=\"56\" HEIGHT=\"12\"   \nBORDER=\"0\" ALT=\"top of page\"></A> \n</TD></TR>\n</TABLE>\n<HR>\n<p><a name=\"story15170\"></a>\n<TABLE WIDTH=\"600\" BORDER=\"0\" CELLPADDING=\"0\" CELLSPACING=\"0\">\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n<TD>\n<h3>Domtar shutting 3 sawmills, 30 MMBF,  due to drop in demand, prices</H3>\n<i>11/08/2001 07:54:09, CNW</i>\n<br><br></TD>\n</TR>\n\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n\t<TD>\nMONTREAL, Nov. 8, 2001 (Canada NewsWire/press release) - Domtar Inc. announced today that it will\ntemporarily halt the production of lumber at its sawmills in Lebel-sur-\nQu?villon, Val d'Or and Ste-Aur?lie (all located in the Province of Quebec)\nfrom November 19th to January 7th, 2002 in an attempt to further balance their\ninventories with demand....<br>\n(<A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15170&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47\">Story...</a>)\n\n</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT>&nbsp;</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT><A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#top\"><IMG SRC=\"http://www.forestweb.com/digest/images/news/top.gif\" align=right WIDTH=\"56\" HEIGHT=\"12\"   \nBORDER=\"0\" ALT=\"top of page\"></A> \n</TD></TR>\n</TABLE>\n<HR>\n<p><a name=\"story15176\"></a>\n<TABLE WIDTH=\"600\" BORDER=\"0\" CELLPADDING=\"0\" CELLSPACING=\"0\">\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n<TD>\n<h3>Votorantim, K-C de Mexico  among JPMorgan's top Latin American picks</H3>\n<i>11/08/2001 09:01:41, BW</i>\n<br><br></TD>\n</TR>\n\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n\t<TD>\nJPMorgan Announces Top Equity Picks for Latin America<pL>\nNEW YORK, Nov. 7, 2001 (Business Wire/press release)--JPMorgan's Latin American equity analysts announced their top stock ideas for the regi...<br>\n(<A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15176&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47\">Story...</a>)\n\n</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT>&nbsp;</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT><A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#top\"><IMG SRC=\"http://www.forestweb.com/digest/images/news/top.gif\" align=right WIDTH=\"56\" HEIGHT=\"12\"   \nBORDER=\"0\" ALT=\"top of page\"></A> \n</TD></TR>\n</TABLE>\n<HR>\n<p><a name=\"story15177\"></a>\n<TABLE WIDTH=\"600\" BORDER=\"0\" CELLPADDING=\"0\" CELLSPACING=\"0\">\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n<TD>\n<h3>Munksjo reports paper earnings stable, big drop for pulp</H3>\n<i>11/08/2001 09:17:13, BW</i>\n<br><br></TD>\n</TR>\n\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=LEFT>\n\t<TD>\nSTOCKHOLM, Nov. 8, 2001 (Business Wire/Press release)--<p>\n\nMunksjo:<p>\n\n    LOW GROWTH DURING THE PERIOD<p>\n\n    -- Invoiced sales increased with 1% to SEK 4,476 million (4,424).<p>\n\n    CON...<br>\n(<A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=liststories&_function=detail&FORESTWEBNEWS_uid1=15177&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47\">Story...</a>)\n\n</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT>&nbsp;</TD></TR>\n<TR VALIGN=TOP ALIGN=RIGHT><TD ALIGN=RIGHT><A HREF=\"/digest/news.control.taf?_section=view&_function=detail&EDITION_ID=2073&_UserReference=3EA50C1997C6ECB53BEABE47#top\"><IMG SRC=\"http://www.forestweb.com/digest/images/news/top.gif\" align=right WIDTH=\"56\" HEIGHT=\"12\"   \nBORDER=\"0\" ALT=\"top of page\"></A> \n</TD></TR>\n</TABLE>\n<HR>\n<br clear=all>\n<DIV align=center>\n<p><table width=\"100%\" border=\"3\" cellspacing=\"0\" cellpadding=\"10\">\n  <tr>\n    <td><font face=\"Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif\" size=\"-1\">To unsubscribe from \n      the Pulp, Writing &amp; Printing Paper News, click on <a href=\"mailto:requests@forestweb.net?subject=unsubscribe%20enronpulp\">UNSUBSCRIBE</a> \n      and simply send the corresponding email. </font></td>\n  </tr>\n</table>\n </p>\n</DIV>\n <br clear=all>\n<DIV align=center>\n<h5 >All news reports are copyrighted by the respective authors.<BR>\npowered by Forestweb</h5>\n</DIV>\n\n</BODY>\n</HTML>", "labels": [[10154, 10183, "email"], [88, 112, "url"], [56, 62, "phone"], [130, 142, "ORG"], [160, 175, "ORG"], [178, 192, "ORG"], [310, 322, "ORG"], [503, 512, "ORG"], [536, 587, "ORG"], [589, 598, "ORG"], [635, 640, "ORG"], [643, 661, "ORG"], [663, 690, "ORG"], [884, 898, "ORG"], [914, 923, "ORG"], [1065, 1084, "ORG"], [1114, 1123, "ORG"], [1267, 1289, "ORG"], [1291, 1310, "ORG"], [1427, 1436, "ORG"], [1642, 1654, "ORG"], [1676, 1686, "GPE"], [1688, 1693, "GPE"], [1866, 1872, "GPE"], [2087, 2094, "GPE"], [2163, 2204, "ORG"], [2546, 2556, "PERSON"], [2558, 2571, "ORG"], [2579, 2587, "ORG"], [2775, 2782, "GPE"], [3142, 3154, "ORG"], [3176, 3186, "GPE"], [3188, 3193, "GPE"], [3212, 3224, "PERSON"], [3319, 3324, "GPE"], [3358, 3374, "ORG"], [3400, 3412, "PERSON"], [3472, 3482, "GPE"], [3484, 3489, "GPE"], [3525, 3532, "ORG"], [3580, 3590, "GPE"], [3592, 3596, "GPE"], [3641, 3648, "ORG"], [4130, 4166, "ORG"], [4378, 4388, "PERSON"], [4414, 4420, "GPE"], [4481, 4493, "GPE"], [4575, 4588, "GPE"], [4604, 4613, "ORG"], [4618, 4624, "GPE"], [4780, 4815, "ORG"], [4819, 4827, "GPE"], [5246, 5282, "ORG"], [5494, 5504, "PERSON"], [5530, 5537, "GPE"], [5691, 5698, "GPE"], [5732, 5751, "ORG"], [6066, 6129, "ORG"], [6229, 6239, "PERSON"], [6289, 6299, "PERSON"], [6335, 6374, "ORG"], [6463, 6499, "ORG"], [6711, 6721, "PERSON"], [6747, 6753, "ORG"], [6906, 6914, "GPE"], [6930, 6951, "ORG"], [6961, 6974, "ORG"], [7065, 7070, "ORG"], [7087, 7095, "PERSON"], [7100, 7111, "ORG"], [7128, 7150, "GPE"], [7265, 7328, "ORG"], [7428, 7438, "PERSON"], [7488, 7498, "PERSON"], [7534, 7573, "ORG"], [7662, 7698, "ORG"], [7910, 7920, "PERSON"], [7946, 7956, "PERSON"], [7958, 7971, "ORG"], [7979, 7987, "ORG"], [8105, 8113, "ORG"], [8145, 8158, "LOC"], [8163, 8171, "GPE"], [8187, 8200, "ORG"], [8710, 8746, "ORG"], [8958, 8968, "PERSON"], [8994, 9001, "GPE"], [9057, 9069, "ORG"], [9141, 9150, "GPE"], [9166, 9185, "ORG"], [9342, 9405, "ORG"], [9505, 9515, "PERSON"], [9565, 9575, "PERSON"], [9611, 9650, "ORG"], [9739, 9775, "ORG"], [10031, 10040, "ORG"], [10091, 10113, "ORG"], [10115, 10134, "ORG"], [10439, 10452, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "John,\n\nThe Power Pool received the required security deposit from Enron Canada\nPower Corporation of $2.8 million yesterday.\n\n\n\nCarol Moline\nFinancial Controller\nPower Pool of Alberta\n(403) 233-4686\ncarol.moline@powerpool.ab.ca", "labels": [[198, 226, "email"], [198, 210, "url"], [183, 192, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [7, 21, "ORG"], [66, 79, "ORG"], [79, 96, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "I believe that now that we have signed, there is no condition precedent that will allow for the board to say no to the deal.  Given the prior understanding we had that this transaction did not require board approval I do not think we can or should ask for that approal now.\n--------------------------\nSent from my BlackBerry Wireless Handheld (www.BlackBerry.net)", "labels": [[344, 362, "url"], [314, 342, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Thanks Lisa.  Is the $2 a fixed rate for every month or does it vary.  Also, do we buy that daily, monthly, or longer term than that?  Are there ever any problems with availability of the transmission (history of curtailments)?  Finally, what do we do with the extra power on the days Air Products doesn't take it (I think I remember the deal being for every day but Tuesdays and Wed or something strange like that)?  I know that is a lot of questions... Thanks for your help.\n\nSteve", "labels": [[7, 11, "PERSON"], [285, 297, "ORG"], [478, 483, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "here you go", "labels": []}
{"text": "I purchase Snohomish Transmission to deliver power from MID C to Montana sys. The Transmission cost is $2.00 per mw. This cost is added in addition to the power price at MID C. The Air Products deal is at MID C.  We fill this position by purchasing at MID C.  I hope this helps. \n\n\nLisa     ", "labels": [[11, 33, "ORG"], [56, 61, "ORG"], [65, 72, "GPE"], [82, 94, "ORG"], [170, 180, "ORG"], [282, 291, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Hi Lisa,\n\nI am working on a Hedging Activity Report that will be sent to E&Y on a weekly basis.  I think Mo is out of the office so I heard that you might be the right person to ask for help.  For the first week, I am using a spreadsheet that Mo sent where he bought some July power at MID C.  It looks like the MID C power along with our NW Del length makes us flat for July at MID C and Montana System Border as well.  My questions are:\n\nHow does power flow between MID C and the other delivery points (like Montana)?\nDo we incur a transmission cost on top of what he bought the power for?\nWe are actually a little long (960 MWh) b/c of the Air Products deal that is a little unique ... what happens to this length?\n\nIf it's easier to explain over the phone, please give me a call at 713-853-4748.  Thanks for your help.\n\nSteve ", "labels": [[785, 793, "phone"], [0, 7, "PERSON"], [73, 76, "LOC"], [243, 245, "ORG"], [286, 294, "ORG"], [339, 345, "ORG"], [379, 384, "ORG"], [389, 410, "ORG"], [468, 473, "ORG"], [510, 517, "GPE"], [643, 655, "ORG"], [824, 829, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "John,\n\nFurther to our conversation last week, this is written notification that the\nPower Pool was required to modify PetroCanada's direct sales/forward\ncontracts with Enron Canada Power due to the sale of the Sundance 3 unit\neffective December 29 HE 1 2001.  The details of these changes are provided\nbelow.\n\n***********************************\nOriginal Contract Number: 138\nTerminated: December 28 HE 24\nSource:  Enron Sundance 3 (Enron's metered asset)\nSink: PO1U\n\nNew Contract Number: 2048\nBegin Date: December 29 HE 1\nExpiry Date: December 31 HE 24\nSource:  Enron ECP- (Enron's unmetered asset)\nSink: PO1U\n***********************************\nOriginal Contract Number: 1287\nTerminated: December 28 HE 24\nSource:  Enron Sundance 3 (Enron's metered asset)\nSink: PO1U\n\nNew Contract Number: 2052\nBegin Date: December 29 HE 1\nExpiry Date: December 31 HE 24\nSource:  Enron ECP- (Enron's unmetered asset)\nSink: PO1U\n***********************************\n\nIf you have any questions relating to this matter, please give me a call.\n\nCarol Moline\nFinancial Controller\nPower Pool of Alberta\n(403) 233-4686\ncarol.moline@powerpool.ab.ca", "labels": [[1096, 1124, "email"], [1096, 1108, "url"], [252, 257, "phone"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [118, 129, "ORG"], [168, 186, "ORG"], [210, 220, "ORG"], [415, 420, "ORG"], [433, 438, "ORG"], [563, 568, "ORG"], [575, 580, "ORG"], [717, 722, "ORG"], [735, 740, "ORG"], [865, 870, "ORG"], [877, 882, "ORG"], [1025, 1038, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Paula,  Tim Detmering talked with Jeff McMahon about this the other night, but Tim isn't in today so I don't know what they decided.  However, in October it was decided by Rick Buy and Pug Winokur that this was not a board action item.  I know a lot has changed since then, so if we want to take this to the board this time we will prepare the information as you suggest.  Would you re-check with Jeff McMahon and Rick Buy and confirm that this will be a board agenda item.  In the interim, Steve Harper will get the listed items in a package.\n\nJeff  ", "labels": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [8, 21, "PERSON"], [34, 46, "PERSON"], [79, 82, "PERSON"], [172, 180, "PERSON"], [185, 196, "PERSON"], [397, 409, "PERSON"], [414, 422, "PERSON"], [491, 503, "PERSON"], [545, 551, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Jeff - We are planning a BoD meeting next Wed.  A Board package for such a transaction would typically include:\n\nExec. summary of transaction\nDASH\nResolution\n\nPlease send at your convenience, but by next Monday for distribution on Tuesday.  Thanks.  Paula", "labels": [[0, 9, "PERSON"], [50, 55, "ORG"], [250, 255, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Greg Whalley has requested a Trader's Meeting tomorrow morning @ 7:45 a.m. (CST).  The meeting will be held in his office, ECS 06752.  The dial-in number for Portland and Calgary is listed below.\n\nDial-in #\t\t888.285.4585\nHost Code:\t869944 (Greg)\nParticipant code:\t107058\n\n\nMany Thanks,\n\nLiz Taylor\nx31935", "labels": [[70, 73, "url"], [126, 132, "phone"], [0, 12, "PERSON"], [29, 35, "ORG"], [123, 132, "ORG"], [158, 166, "GPE"], [171, 178, "GPE"], [240, 244, "PERSON"], [287, 297, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Hi Sabrina.  \n\n  Sorry it has taken me a while to get back to you on this.  Jenny Thome and Lisa Gang are working on Avista true-up from Jan '02 thru current. I believe that this pre-payment for $899,464.00 is for the week of Jan 1 thru Jan 7, 2002.  Mo - can you please confirm this?  The wire transfer request is pending 26, but  just says prepay without a trade date.  Payment was made 12/21/02.\n\n  Virginia", "labels": [[196, 203, "phone"], [0, 10, "PERSON"], [76, 87, "PERSON"], [92, 101, "PERSON"], [402, 410, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "I assume this has to go before our board before we sign, right??\n\n\nJeffrey McMahon\n___________________________\nExecutive Vice President &\nChief Financial Officer\nEnron Corp\n713-853-5359 phone\n713-646-5930 fax\njeffrey.mcmahon@enron.com", "labels": [[209, 234, "email"], [209, 224, "url"], [173, 180, "phone"], [67, 82, "PERSON"], [136, 138, "ORG"], [162, 173, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Sorry,,,I forgot to attach the press .release\n\n << File: INDIA - EOGIL NEW AGREEMENT - DRAFT 7.doc >> ", "labels": [[93, 98, "url"], [57, 62, "GPE"]]}
{"text": "Jeff,  FYI here is the game plan for EOGIL and the sale to BG.  \n1) It appears that we have the fundamental support of the creditor committee to sign the BG deal for India. (See Tim's note below)\n2) I spoke to Ray by telephone(on his way to the airport) regarding the questions Lilly Chu had outlined when she spoke to Tim Detmering.\n3) To paraphrase Ray's comments to my note below, a) he is working with the creditors' committee on the D&O issues and both the committee and Ray want to put a broader program in place to handle our concerns for the asset sales and the on-going business.  At this point we are in good faith proceeding with the sale with the assumption that this will be sorted out before we sign the deal in mid-February.  b) the deal compensation should sort itself out as the appropriate people review the information they have been given over the weekend and today.  As a non-debtor we plan to honor the agreements, but we will supply Lilly et al with the information they need to understand the deal in place. \n4) With these understandings we are proceeding forward to sign the documents with BG and file a motion with the court.\n4) Brian Rosen is drafting the motion for the court and he will circulate it tomorrow for comments and expect to file it ASAP.  The hearing date will be in mid-February.\n5) Tim is in discussions with BG and the only outstanding issue is the escrow \"form of agreement\".  This will be either resolved this evening or put to the side until closing since it is not needed for signing.  However, BG is making noise that they would like to finalize it if possible before signing this evening. \n6) THEREFORE ASSUMING THE STARS ALIGN and WE SIGN THE DEAL TONIGHT, BG WILL BE ISSUING A PRESS RELEASE TOMORROW.  A COPY IS ATTACHED.  WE HAVE SENT IT THROUGH PR (John Ambler & Johan Zaayman) and the working group and now the two of you.  Do we need to send it elsewhere?   \n\nWe'll circulate a short note if and when we execute the documents.\n\nIf you have any questions or comments please contact Tim, Stephen or I.\n\njeff", "labels": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [37, 42, "ORG"], [59, 61, "ORG"], [119, 141, "ORG"], [154, 156, "ORG"], [166, 171, "GPE"], [178, 181, "PERSON"], [210, 213, "PERSON"], [278, 287, "PERSON"], [319, 332, "PERSON"], [351, 354, "PERSON"], [438, 441, "ORG"], [476, 479, "PERSON"], [1155, 1166, "PERSON"], [1325, 1328, "PERSON"], [1352, 1354, "ORG"], [1543, 1545, "ORG"], [1803, 1814, "PERSON"], [1817, 1830, "PERSON"], [2037, 2040, "PERSON"], [2042, 2049, "PERSON"], [2053, 2061, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "With respect to the note below,  we have done the following this morning.  \n1) We have provided Mary Jean Potenzone with Weil samples of the documents for her review.  There are a couple of different documents (Retention agreements & divestiture agreements) and the only differences being names and amounts.  We have also sent her any associated agreements, extensions and assignment.  She indicated she would review this afternoon.  My understanding is she is the conduit to Millbank.  \n\n2) None of the people on this list participated in the pre-petition retention Lilly has asked about.  Futhermore, none of these people are part of the future plan (if there is one) to the best of my knowledge.\n\n3) On D&O, supposedly Lilly said they discussed this and the creditors' see the need for such a plan but they don't want a one off plan as well.  It would be good to get someone on behalf of the creditors to send us a written note along these lines.  \n\n4)  Once we have the compensation and the D&O issue resolved, we can notify BG and sign this deal.  I suggest you call Lilly and get closure on these two issues (ok on bonuses & letter in lieu of D&O policy) if you can.\n\n5) Brian is drafting the motion and he just informed us that neither of these issues need to be in the motion, they are just creditor committee issues.\n\njeff", "labels": [[96, 115, "PERSON"], [476, 484, "ORG"], [567, 572, "ORG"], [706, 709, "ORG"], [722, 727, "ORG"], [995, 998, "ORG"], [1029, 1031, "ORG"], [1072, 1077, "ORG"], [1149, 1152, "ORG"], [1177, 1182, "PERSON"]]}
{"text": "Just spoke with Lilly Chu at Houlihan.  The Creditor's Committee is fine with the transaction with the following reservations:\n\t1)  Escrow the proceeds\n\t2)  D&O insurance will be addressed in the future\t\n\t3)  Ray needs to get back with Lilly and clarify the deal compensation arrangements for EGEP personnel including providing employment agreements to Milbank.  Lilly was confused about who was participating in the deal compensation and expressed concern about making clear that people are only getting paid once, i.e., people who got a piece of the pre-petition retention were not also getting a deal bonus for this transaction and were not also getting something out of the upcoming retention plan.\n\t4)  EGEP showed up on a chart that we sent her as a Debtor.  I told her that was incorrect and apologized for Eickenroht's mistake.  ( I just assumed it was Robert since he was not in the room at the time.)\n\t\nTherefore, the Creditors are please to have us file our motion so long as it provides for escrowing the proceeds, does not provide for separate D&O insurance and does not address the deal compensation.", "labels": [[516, 519, "url"], [16, 25, "PERSON"], [29, 37, "ORG"], [40, 64, "ORG"], [157, 160, "ORG"], [209, 212, "PERSON"], [236, 241, "ORG"], [293, 297, "ORG"], [353, 360, "ORG"], [363, 368, "ORG"], [814, 824, "ORG"], [861, 867, "PERSON"], [1057, 1060, "ORG"]]}
{"text": "Jennifer,\nYes, I do believe you have the correct understanding.  The ttls you have tie to the dms impact. Let me know if you have any questions.\n\nThanks,\nElsie", "labels": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [154, 159, "PERSON"]]}
